<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Michael Veale</title>
    <link>http://michae.lv/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Michael Veale</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="http://michae.lv/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>publications</title>
      <link>http://michae.lv/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michae.lv/publications/</guid>
      <description>2018  Veale M., Van Kleek M., &amp;amp; Binns R. (2018). Fairness and accountability design needs for algorithmic support in high-stakes public sector decision-making. Proceedings of the 2018 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems (CHI&amp;rsquo;18). [mirror]   We interviewed 27 public sector, machine learning practitioners about how they cope with challenges of fairness and accountability. Their problems are often different from those in FAT/ML research so far, including internal gaming, changing data distributions and inter-departmental communication, how to augment model outputs and how to transmit hard-won social practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>talks</title>
      <link>http://michae.lv/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michae.lv/talks/</guid>
      <description>“Fairness and Accountability Design Needs for Algorithmic Support in High-Stakes Public Sector Decision-Making .” ACM Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems — CHI’18, Montreal, Canada. April 2018
 “Better Seen and Note (Over)heard? Automatic Lipreading Systems and Privacy in Public Spaces”, BILETA, Aberdeen, 10 March 2018
 “Eavesdropping whilst you’re shopping: Balancing Personalisation and Privacy in Connected Retail Spaces”. “Living in the IoT” IET PETRAS Conference 2018. 28 February 2018</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>